<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<presets>
	<preset>
		<name>No preset (manual configuration)</name>
		<value>none</value>
	</preset>
	<preset>
		<name>Case study 1: NES/CRM1 candidates in human proteins of Cajal bodies</name>
		<description>This preset illustrates a basic search using the NES/CRM1 motif for searching candidates in a subproteome.
		We target reviewed human proteins in UniProt that are annotated with the term GO:0015030 (Cajal body). A
		score threshold of 50 is used to focus on the best candidates.</description>
		<value>case1</value>
		<mainMotif>NES/CRM1</mainMotif>
		<threshold>50</threshold>
		<target>UniProtKB/Swiss-Prot Human Subproteome</target>
		<targetInput>GO:0015030 (Cajal body)</targetInput>
	</preset>
	<preset>
		<name>Case study 2: NES/CRM1 candidates with auxiliar NLS motif in Cargo A proteins (Kirli et al., 2015)</name>
		<description>This case shows an example of using an auxiliary motif. We use NES/CRM1 as the main motif but we are also
		interested in the presence of a predicted NLS in the same protein. We target a positive dataset (Cargo A) to
		corroborate that the presence of an auxiliary NLS motif is significantly higher than in a negative dataset (Non-binder).</description>
		<value>case2</value>
		<mainMotif>NES/CRM1</mainMotif>
		<auxMotif>TRG_NLS_MonoCore_2</auxMotif>
		<target>Cargo A</target>
	</preset>
	<preset>
		<name>Case study 3: Combining PLK4 motif matches with dbPTM phosphorilations in human centrosome</name>
		<description>This is an example of using PTM information. We use the PLK4 motif to find potential phosphorylation sites and also
		check if there are already known phosphorylations at those positions. Since this phosphorylation is spatially
		restricted to structures such as the centrosome, we target a subset of the HPA centrosome proteins that we will use
		for training a custom PSSM using only phosphorylated matches.</description>
		<value>case3</value>
		<mainMotif>MOD_Plk_4</mainMotif>
		<target>Custom list of human UniProtKB/Swiss-Prot accessions</target>
		<targetInput>P25786 Q8N0Z9 Q9NQ84 Q8TCT7 O14775 O94986 Q5SRH9 Q8N2W9 Q7Z7E8 Q8NET8 O95684 Q9H488 Q96LK0 Q96FT9 Q9Y6Q1 O75934 O60271 Q5SXH7 Q6P2H3 P98155 A1L390 Q15004 Q6NZ67 Q8TF20 Q9H1Y0 Q9HBG7 P08754 Q2TBC4 Q8N137 Q7Z5J8 Q96QP1 Q86VF5 Q7Z6G8 Q9BV97 Q86XU0 Q9Y6A5 Q8N7B1 P51861 Q8WU08 Q14008 Q8IUG5 Q69YU5 P21580 Q96BT1 Q13564 Q92772 O96006 Q96CS2 Q8TBC4 Q86TZ1 Q9UHG0 P42081 Q8IWU2 P16870 Q96AZ1 Q8WYA6 Q8NCE0 Q86SQ7 Q8IVH8 O75815 A0A0B4J2D5 O75449 O95757 Q8TDW4 P41208 Q52LW3 Q5SVZ6 Q68DE3 Q9Y3D8 Q04759 Q96GX8 P47972 Q8N3F8 Q9H2S5 Q9BQD3 P12271 P43007 Q9Y4W2 Q8NFI3 Q9BRT9 Q01968 B6SEH9 Q4JDL3 O94830 Q9BRR6 Q9UPN4 Q5T3J3 B6SEH8 Q8IZS7 Q4ZJI4 Q7Z4N2 Q9H9D4 Q8WXW3 Q15154 Q9HD42 Q02833 Q9H2A2 Q6N043 Q99661 Q5BKX5 Q6ZMV9 Q8TC17 Q9C0H6 P50135 Q8TBB0 B1ATL7 Q8IXQ3 O00241 Q12873 Q86VE9 Q96IW2 Q9H944 Q16513 Q8IYE1 A2A368 Q8N4P2 Q9H981 Q8N8E3 O75923 P50238 Q9P209 Q12756 O00139 Q9H6Y7 Q49A88 O00463 P03901 Q9HCK4 P24394 Q8WWK9 Q9Y4I1 Q9H9A5 Q8ND07 Q8IZJ4 Q86YS7 Q02363 P50607 P0C025 P49356 Q9NXL2 Q8WVC0 O43169 Q96DB5 P17014 O43303 P39687 Q8WVS4 Q8WUM4 Q9NZL4 Q9H5V9 Q3MIP1 Q9BXC1 Q9P260 Q8TCU4 P58317 P57740 Q9C019 P42679 Q9BZM4 Q9UN36 Q9NQR4 Q8IY45 Q4LDG9 Q3YEC7 Q9NUD7 Q5TFQ8 O15327 Q00013 Q9H694 Q9BX66 Q8NDH2 Q15691 Q2NKX8 Q86YR7 Q9UJU3 Q5T4S7 O43283 Q9NR16 A6NDN3 Q5M8T2 P86452 Q8IX90 Q86WI3 Q13485 Q8IZ52 Q3ZCU0 O14745 Q16851 Q7Z6K3 Q9UGJ1 Q3SY56 P43034 O15078 O00592 Q0JRZ9 Q8TCG5 Q7Z695 Q7Z7A4 Q99996 Q96ER9 A6NDK9 Q9GZN2 P20336 Q9NQS1 O14777 B3KS81 Q8N813 Q9P1Y5 Q02763 O15182 Q7RTR2 Q70YC5 Q8TF47 Q9Y230 Q6IMN6 Q9ULI2 Q8WZ60 P0DKX4 Q9NVX0 Q9NQL2 Q9ULM0 O43237 O95164 Q86VV8 Q8IVU9 Q8NFJ8 Q9BQF6 P59190 Q8TES7 Q9BYJ4 Q9HC56 Q719H9 Q14204 Q96JH7 Q5VVC0 O60641 P11413 Q8N3T6 Q9H1Z4 Q9UJQ1 Q3B7T1 Q5JSJ4 Q9C040 Q8TEU7 O75419 O00444 P51843 Q9P1W3 Q2LD37 Q3KR16 Q9UK97 Q8WYA0 Q86YF9 Q9NYL4 Q9BRX9 Q15762 Q14393 Q2T9J0 Q96DN5 Q9BSU3 Q7Z591 Q92688 Q8IWC1 Q5TZA2 O43379 Q9NWM3 Q9ULZ0 Q6PF15 A8MZ97 Q13045 O43426</targetInput>
		<dbPtm>true</dbPtm>
		<ptm>Phosphorylation</ptm>
	</preset>
</presets>